hey there thanks for listening to grow
Your Life podcast my name is Jeremiah
Kowski and in this podcast I talk about
ways for you to grow in your life your
business as a coach course creator
Mentor trainer I have over 20 years of
experience successfully in this industry
generating close to a Mund million
dollar in sales and I can help you scale
your business to get more results and
that's what this podcast is all about
that's why I exist on the Internet is to
help you get extremely rich selling
online courses and coaching
now there's something I want to talk
about today super
controversial uh I get a lot of hate
forward online a lot of people who
disagree with me there's a lot of posts
out there about it and it's something
that I just keep seeing rising up and up
and up stronger and stronger and
stronger is this
notion that you are not allowed to sell
courses and coaching until you reach a
certain level of tangible accolades and
experience from years years and years of
experience and that you're actually
somehow wrong to give advice and to
share
advice on things that maybe you're just
learning uh that you're documenting your
journey of and that maybe you might even
be a beginner on and I have a problem
with this because I see it as a form of
gatekeeping a way to keep people poor
and I have problems with things that are
mental framework works that are designed
to keep people poor that's all it
is I truly believe that every single
person you included if you're listening
to this right now that you could create
six
figures selling digital courses and
online coaching and you don't need to be
the world's top ofth the- Mountain
expert and this is coming from somebody
who I would consider myself to be a top
5% expert in the online marketing
digital coaching and digital course
space with my 20 years of successful
experience selling in this space as far
as people who teach you sales teach you
marketing and here's the thing I of
course I
[Music]
am motivated to encourage people to get
out there sell a bunch of courses sell
coaching because my system is teaching
you how to do that okay and so yeah I'm
biased in that position because I
believe that anybody with any level of
experience with any amount of track
record even without case studies can
successfully make six figures selling
digital courses coaching training and
even writing books and now with
artificial intelligence it's even
simpler and easier and I have a problem
with this messaging from people that's
trying to tell people that they're not
qualified enough to do so until they
quote unquote check off some madeup box
that somebody invented one day to say
okay now you're good enough to go do
this
and maybe part of that comes from my
background of being homeschooled and
being told my whole life that I didn't
know enough to be successful that I was
going to have my entire life ruined that
I was never going to be successful
because gosh you don't experience what
kids experience in
school and so you're stunted Jeremiah in
some way those things those curses that
people spoke over my life I never let
them stop
me I never let them stop me and I and I
believe that it's a
curse that people try to speak over
people's lives that say you have no
right to sell digital courses and
coaching until you reach the top level
of
experience in your field it's just it's
it's it's nauseating to Me overall and
and I get it I have empathy for
it I understand there's enough huers and
frauders and charlatan out there
marketing bad
products but I but what I'm really
speaking to is the is the
well-intentioned people out there and I
think that's that's my market that I
connect with the most is the people that
they have a dream they're growing in
their skill set and here's the thing
from my experience I have successfully
worked with mentors and coaches who are
starting out in a
niche they're not the like oh my gosh
I'm the top 1% in the world in their
niche in fact they don't know much more
than a
beginner but they had some success and
now they're teaching other people how to
do it and I have no problem with that I
have no problem with you learning
something brand new and teaching others
and for me to share this it actually
puts a risk on my reputation I have
people all the time who claim that I
just read a book yesterday and learned
it and un teaching people stuff that I
just learned yesterday well of course uh
they don't know my track record they
don't know my experience they don't know
I've been in this industry for over two
decades that I'm literally like a great
grandpa in the digital marketing space
that I come from uh a family with my mom
who's been in the online marketing space
for three
decades that we have been Pioneers in
the space of online sales and market so
it's I'm like you know I just kind of
laugh when people tell me that I'm
disqualified to even say what I'm saying
it's hilarious to me uh but I have a
problem with people trying to disqualify
others saying that they're not quote
unquote good enough to be able to sell
courses and
coaching it's all about how you frame it
I'm not encouraging you to sell things
scammy or scummy or to lie to people
about experience that you don't have be
honest with it but you can still
sell stuff that maybe you have beginning
level experience in you know a great
example of this and I'll tell you my mom
is one I'm not sure if she fully agrees
with me me on this topic and I'm okay
with
that I I I've had some debates with her
about it but her own track record points
to the fact that you know three years
ago she knew nothing about stock market
training and today she has a
multi-million dollar business coaching
people on stocks with just three years
of experience now she has developed
experience she's grown her portfolio but
she started teaching this two years ago
when she only had one year of experience
and she was still learning the
process and yet she was helping people
learn what she knew from her experience
documenting her journey and impacting
people's lives and we've seen the case
studies people generating multi6 figure
stock portfolios my mom has generated a
million-dollar stock portfolio with that
limited experience but didn't stop her
from putting that out there marketing
and selling to people at all and so
listen I want to encourage you stop
letting this belief that you're not good
enough yet to Market and sell to people
this fear of disappointing others this
fear of I need to be perfect before I
can put myself out there it's all pride
and
ego it's all pride and ego and it comes
from somewhere along the line somebody
might have told you to not do things
unless you're perfect at them or the top
level at them or the highest quality at
them
listen there's always room for
improvement in
everything there's always room for
improvement in everything my mom could
get better at trading stocks I can get
better at teaching coaching even though
I've been it in it for 20 years I still
am
improving so does that mean that I
should quit my business shut it down
because I'm not at the level yet of
somebody else or that my mom should shut
her business down until she quote
unquote reaches has a certain level of
experience to where she's finally
qualified enough to do it according to
what some people might
say no and yet that's the standard that
I see people put themselves and others
through this standard of gatekeeping
that says that you have no right to
Mentor Market coach train or create
courses until you are the top
dog and it's a problem it's a real
problem sales doesn't care about your
experience being able to sell has to do
with your ability to persuade others to
believe that you have the solution to
the problem they have and that you will
deliver a result and that has zero to do
with your actual track record and that's
what most people have a problem with is
that it's actually very easy to
sell crap to
people it it is it's easy to sell crap
when you know how to sell you can make a
ton of money selling stuff that maybe
you have no experience
in I have a middle ground that I take on
this though as long as you are working
towards increasing your skill
set you're more than qualified to go out
there create a course change your
family's future impact the lives of your
students with information that maybe you
even just learned
recently
and so I encourage people and listen
whether you agree with this ethically or
not with me at the end of the day it
really doesn't matter to my bottom line
because I help people get super rich
selling courses and coaching because our
methods are the best on the planet at
selling them at getting
clients okay and so with that I would
encourage you create a course create a
coaching program join our program learn
to sell them become extremely wealthy
then go invest your earnings in stocks
go join my mom's stocks community and
invest in stocks and grow your portfolio
change your family's Destiny literally
my entire
family has changed our
future gone from living on welfare when
I was growing up to living literally
being in the top point
0.001% of people in our country of
wealth and that happened by being
willing to take a risk and not have to
do what other people tell us to do did
you know that financial success follows
you going against what everybody else
tells you you quote unquote should do
and yet why are we letting people tell
us what we should do or what we're
qualified enough to do and to dictate
what we're allowed to do to open our
mouth I have such a problem with this
telling people they need to be silent
whoever gave you the right to speak on
that topic I've had a problem with this
for
years I really have because I Empower
people to find their voice to activate
what's deep inside of them that they
might not have words for and now with AI
with chat GPT we got words for it if you
struggle to explain something but you
know it up here you can feel it right
here you can explain it to AI like chat
GPT and it can literally help you craft
an argument that is strong and Powerful
to actually share your thoughts with
people I do it on a regular basis when I
struggle to actually express
myself but I got a big problem with
people telling people what they can and
can't
do simply because they quote unquote
haven't reached some madeup
level of hitting a high score of some
kind it's just it's Petty it's weak
and I'd rather see people get extremely
rich while taking risks and having fun
in the process than holding themselves
back when there's opportunity to change
their life instead of where the middle
class is being eroded and eliminated and
all we have is the wealthy and the poor
seeing people go into the poor bracket
when they could literally become wealthy
and that's what I have more of a problem
with and that's why I'm passionate about
seeing
people change their lives with courses
and coaching and that's why I do what I
do that's why I feel called to do what I
do that's why I feel called to be a
voice in this area that I'm talking
about even if the top gurus tell me I'm
wrong even if the top gurus tell me I
should not be telling people
this I'm okay with that I'm okay with
disappointing other people I'm okay with
people disagreeing with me if I can help
change a family's future with their
income I did my job and I want to see
you become extremely wealthy all right
so grow your life don't let anybody tell
you what you can and can't do we'll talk
soon have a good
[Music]
[Applause]
one